For interest and inflation here for Hexatronic.
So I will stay with my shares.
It is not often that I usually make such comments.
But I will stay there.
I will not buy more because the holding is a little too heavy in my portfolio right now.
So we'll see how it goes.
We keep our thumbs because it may be that the market re -evaluates its views on the share a little further ahead.
But it was a small short report comment at Hexatronic.
Hope you appreciated it.
In such cases, please put a thumbs up and so on.
And if you want to know what I buy and sell for something in real time, you can become a member on the channel.
Thanks to all the members and you who are watching and subscribing.
Have a good time!
Ciao!